The most important part of your body to train is your core.
Your lower body is vital.
If you are able to stabilize yourself with a robust lower body,
it will lead to having more accurate attacks and an unwavering defense.
You'll begin your training here by cold plunging in the waterfall.
I'm gonna die!
After which I'll have you lift up these three logs.
Shh. They're huge.
Last but not least, you'll push this boulder one chou away from where it stands.
And that's all I have for you.
My training consists of these three simple tasks.
As it would be dangerous to have you sit atop fire, I have omitted it.
Excuse me, but I think Zenichou has fainted!
Put him in the river for a bit.
Let's get out of sync.
答えを示す時だ 無限に続く螺旋の先
.
the
You're right there you're right there you're right there you're right there you're
Hama no yomi shi wo tsudaru
Uba teku uba teku
Arash no yori koko lo u saku
Eijen no yimi shiraru kimi ni
Kotae wo shimezu toki ta
Nu geu ni tutsuku wase no saki ni
Kotae wo wa teku
GAAAH! IT'S FREEZING!
IT'S THE WINTER! WHY WOULD YOU THROW ME IN A RIVER WHEN IT'S THE WINTER?
I'M GONNA THROW UP AND DIE!
Send me back on land! Hurry! Oh crap!
My organs are smashing! HELP ME! I'M GONNA DIE!
No, it's too late! I'm out but I'm still freezing to dead!
Long time no see
Come try this
Cling to the boulders
They're nice and warm
It's so warm!
I never knew boulders could feel like this
It's like I'm being held in my mother's arms again
It's freezing!
This is really tough!
Waterfall training is brutal!
Coming through, coming through, coming through, coming through, coming through
It's not working!
If Inosuke is giving it us all then I can too
Huh?
Why'd he suddenly stop chanting?
Huh? Inosuke?
No! Hey! This is bad! Really bad!
Inosuke! Wake up Inosuke! Wake up! Inosuke! Wake up!
Is that you, Mantra? Inosuke!
Coming through
This waterfall's massive
And it's not just any waterfall
Whatever you do, don't stop chanting the Nenbutsu!
Sure, it helps you focus a little bit
But it's also a signal to others that you're still conscious, okay?
Right
The water is freezing and heavy
Come on, you've gotta be quiet
Nenbutsu, Nenbutsu
Nenbutsu, Nenbutsu, Nenbutsu, Nenbutsu Nenbutsu, Nenbutsu Nenbutsu!
So cold!
All we're doing is standing under the waterfall but it sure isn't tense
How new water cascading from down from so high feels that heavy?
If you relaxed your body too much, you could break your neck.
No way.
Both you and that boar are truly amazing.
My first day, it took me until the evening to get the hang of it.
Even then, it still feels cold.
It took me a while, but now that I'm able to stay under the waterfall for two hours,
I'm finally moving on to the log training.
I'm so happy for you, Mr. Murata.
Well, it did take me ten days.
That old guy's insane.
The one with the rattling beads.
Mr. Himejima, the stone Hashira?
Careful with the nicknames you give people.
The moment I first met him, it gave me the chills.
You're eating the bones, Inosuke?
Yeah, why?
You're not going to eat yours?
They're crunchy and tasty.
Wow.
Of all the people I know, no one can eat a fish cleaner than you can, Inosuke.
You must have forgotten I'm the king of the mountains.
Of course I do.
Are you going to be okay?
That's your tenth fish today.
Anyway, about that old guy with the rattling beads.
Mr. Himejima, the stone Hashira, right?
There's not a doubt in my mind.
He's the strongest one in the core.
Wow.
You think so, too?
Huh?
Is that true?
Mr. Himejima's scent is totally different from everyone else's.
I wonder if his mark has already shown up.
You wouldn't be surprised if it has.
These guys have shot up their ranks so fast, I can't even keep up with their conversations anymore.
It's like they're speaking a different language.
It's so next level.
It's beyond me.
Wow.
The fish Tanjiro grilled are excellent.
Yeah.
Well, I don't believe it.
I bet that old guy can't even move a huge boulder like that one Chou himself.
He's just having a blast tormenting us.
No, really.
I hear Mr. Himejima is able to push even bigger boulders than that one.
Do you just believe anything you hear from anyone?
He's lying to you.
I don't think so.
But hey, your hearing is great, Zenitsu.
So I'm sure you'll be able to tell if he's lying or not.
Oh, look, there he is right now.
Wow.
He's incredible, isn't he, Zenitsu?
You think I'll ever get to be like him?
In your dreams, muscle head!
What are you, a moron?
Hello?
Is anyone home in there?
That old guy is just abnormal.
I mean, look at him.
He looks more bare than human.
Shut up.
There's a gap between people like him and people like us from birth.
Do you understand?
All right.
Now that I'm full, I'm going to leave some logs and shove a boulder.
Shut up.
Why are you all being so positive?
We're separate.
There, there.
Let's go!
Zenitsu!
Wait!
Waterfall training completed!
At last, it's time.
It seems I've found another one of them.
I've now located around 60% of the Demon Slayer core members.
Though it matters not, as I've yet to locate the girl who managed to conquer the sun.
Oh, Nakime, how you've grown, you've become far more valuable than I ever imagined.
How magnificent.
It is an honor to hear you say that.
Let's see what's left to peruse.
How about around here?
Let me see what I can find.
it seems we found two more of them try your best to keep following them undetected
understood as you wish
soon both Nezuko and Ubuyashiki will run out of places to hide from me
it's no use my legs keep slipping no I'm losing ground
that hurt
I should go back and fix it
morning everyone
oh Commodore
we're heading back down the mountain now
it's become too much for us
sorry we feel really guilty about bailing on training like this
but we'll be more useful to you all as support
best of luck
Commodore
thanks I'm counting on you all
what on us
if you provide us support in the future
then we can fight the demons without any worries
it's going to take all of us together
to beat Muzan Kibutsuji
you got it
you leave the backup to us
Roger that Kamado
we got this
that's right
there's no room for failure
wow
you're really good at making those Tanjiro
no kidding they're practically perfect
since we've been running ourselves ragged
I added a little extra salt
thank you all for being patient
dig in
wow
oh this is amazing
it really hits the spot huh
yeah it does
you know
I realized something during this training
I finally get why the current Hashira don't have Tsukoko
why don't they
I have a feeling I now know why too
it's too exhausting
I bet they all ran off
yeah
or maybe it's like what happened with that blonde guy
his soul's been crushed
by the difference between himself and the Hashira
the Hashira really are incredible
to be able to do all this
not to mention how easy they make it look
they really are huh
I doubt any of them could cook rice as good as this though
yum
yeah
and he can grill fish like a champ
thank you
I am the son of a charcoal burger
oh no wonder
it's all about the right heat
grilled rice balls are good too
way to go Tanjiro
please eat as much as you want
tastes great
this miso flavored one is amazing
it's so good I'm crying
I know right
tastes like mom's cooking
yeah
it does
mommy
mother
somehow
this brings back memories
no good today either
it's been six days though
what do I do
it's not like the demons will stay inactive like this forever
I have to hurry
is it just that I don't have enough muscular strength
or is there another breathing technique I need to learn
even after all this brutal training
I still can't maintain my mark
hey you
is it me or did your mark get darker
ah
Genya
how are you holding up
I couldn't get a hold of you after what happened
so I was worried
yeah I was being reprimanded
Mr. Himejima gave me an earful
I guess I understand it after what happened with my brother
they did tell me to avoid him
oh I see
sorry I dragged you into that
thank you for defending me
oh it was nothing
anyway
about that mark of yours
oh
does it look any darker
yeah
no one ever mentioned that to me up till now
well after looking at it every day
how could they spot the difference
do you have a mirror you can use
mm-mm
I could just lend you mine later
it really did get darker
thank goodness
what a relief
kill yourself
ha
sure if you do first
so you're doing the boulder training right
I am too
yeah
but I can't get it to budge at all
have you been able to move it
yeah of course
what
it's simple
just use repetitive motion
huh
you don't know what that is do you
well not like Mr. Himejima is good at teaching it
you need to watch him for yourself to learn it
to enhance your concentration to its very limits
you have to perform a predetermined action
so in my case
I chant the nenbutsu
Mr. Himejima does that
that's right
he says namu namu
namu
so long sucker
don't ever come back here
later
thanks for the help
I'll give it a try
don't overdo it
not that he'd listen to me
that guy's stubborn as a rock
one more time
repetitive motion
remember everything that Genya told you
you have to open up all of your senses at once
according to Mr. Himejima
even though I can't use breathing techniques
I can still move that boulder
as long as I use repetitive motion
well not that I've made much headway myself yet
when Genya and Mr. Himejima use this technique
they rage reliving their most painful memories
by doing that they increase their heart rate and body temperature
damn it
I barely moved it
Tanjiro
can you make dinner for us again tonight?
after tasting that amazing meal you made for us
we can't think of eating anything else
oh it's dinner time already?
I'd better start cooking
you're such a mom
our mom
oh hey Genya
I'll help out too
thank you
so
did the repetitive motion work?
seems like it's different than total concentration
the way I see it
it's like working up your emotions
oh and
it's just a thought
but isn't the mark on your forehead
a sign that you're in that same state
as repetitive motion?
that neither Mr. Himejima
or you
have a mark and you can move it
yeah well
you're right about that
hmm
Tanjiro
in your case
when was it that your emotions
were really worked up in the past?
probably
forget I asked that
it probably brought back a lot of horrible memories
my bad
look I know that you can do it
thank you
by using repetitive motion
you can increase your concentration to its utmost at any time
my repetitive motion is to first
picture the faces of the loved ones that I lost
and also
to recall Mr. Rengoku's words to me
set your heart ablaze
I can feel my mark growing darker
I only hope that I can learn to maintain this state that I'm in
it's Tanpachiru
you're kidding me
why would he want to start training before the sun's even come up yet?
or burn himself out
I can't let him get ahead of me
though I wasn't able to do it properly at first
I exerted all my strength through repetitive motion
and after repeating it
over and over and over again
my body began to master it
from repetitive motion
come strength
keep repeating it
no way
he did it
Tanjiro did it
damn it
you beat me
he's become a monster
what is that man scheming behind this veil of silence
more importantly
what am I to do in the meantime
the day I find out what you look like Ubuyashiki
will be your last
you
I!
Remember, as you love, coming with your eyes
That is the times I reach my days
My soul, freakin' bunch of hours
Under dawn's beloved
Like I said to myself
neurology and Hammond
Is still engaging
Today, we're going to talk about Mr. Himejima.
Is something wrong, Mr. Himejima?
So innocent.
Alright, here's a Taisho era secret.
Mr. Himejima cries more than you would think.
I hear that if he finds a messy room, that it's enough to make him cry.
Namo, this cat is cute.
Namo, this cat is so cute.
And he's in tears again.
Next, Episode 7, The Stone Hashira Gyomei Himejima.